paperlessemployee.com 2019-07-06

# Default - PaperlessEmployee.com

  1. Introduction

1.1  In the ordinary course of providing services to its clients, CIC Plus receives personal information from its clients about their current and former employees. In some cases, we also receive information about that employee’s dependents and family members.

1.2  This Privacy Statement explains our practices with regard to the personal information we receive, obtain, process, and store for our clients.

1.3  Depending on the services we provide for a client, this information could include a person’s name, address, social security number, email address, phone number, passwords and security data, payment information, and certain wage and tax information. CIC Plus receives and processes that personal information as provided for in the contract we have with our client (your employer).

1.4  When a user accesses our website, their IP address, browser, and device characteristics are collected automatically.

  2. Protecting Personal Information

2.1  CIC Plus is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the personal information we receive and process in order to provide services to our clients. 

2.2  CIC Plus maintains appropriate security controls to protect that information. We have implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative safeguards to help protect the personal information from unlawful use and unauthorized disclosure.

2.3  All CIC Plus employees are required to follow established procedures for protecting personal information. Access to personal information is limited to those associates who need to access that information in connection with the services CIC Plus provides to its clients.

  3. Disclosing Personal Information

3.1  CIC Plus will disclose your personal information to your employer and to other entities when needed as part of the services we provide to our client.

3.2  On occasion, we may send an employee news or other information about their account or employer, our products, or the services we provide.

3.3  We may disclose your personal data to a third-party processor as needed to provide the services that your employer has requested. These entities are contractually bound to limit the use of your personal information as needed to perform the services.

3.4  We will also disclose personal data when required to do so by law, such as in response to a subpoena, including to law enforcement agencies and courts in the United States.

3.5  We do not sell or otherwise use an employee’s personal information for marketing purposes.

  4. Warranty & Conditions

4.1  As a condition of using our website, you promise that you will not use our website for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices.

4.2  You may not use our website in any manner, which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the website or interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the website.

4.3  You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the website.

4.4  By using this site, you are agreeing to the terms set forth here.

4.5  We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.
